<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>GWC Library on Girls Who Code at UNC Charlotte</title><link>https://gwc-uncc.github.io/Girls-Who-Code-at-UNCC/library/</link><description>Recent content in GWC Library on Girls Who Code at UNC Charlotte</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 01:56:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gwc-uncc.github.io/Girls-Who-Code-at-UNCC/library/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>GWC is Collecting Donations For GWC T-Shirts</title><link>https://gwc-uncc.github.io/Girls-Who-Code-at-UNCC/library/gwc-is-collecting-donations-for-gwc-t-shirts/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 01:56:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gwc-uncc.github.io/Girls-Who-Code-at-UNCC/library/gwc-is-collecting-donations-for-gwc-t-shirts/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="more-information">&lt;strong>M﻿ORE INFORMATION&lt;/strong>&lt;/h1>
&lt;h2 id="currently-accepting-donations-up-to-october-13th">C﻿urrently Accepting donations up to October 13th&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>W﻿e are very committed to not only providing our members with a mixture of fun, professional and technical events but also giving back to our members. This is the first semester we are providing our members with t-shirts and of course, as a large organization, projects like these can be costly. That is why we are reaching out to you, GWC alumni, an esteemed partner of GWC, a current member of GWC, or even a fellow member of the Charlotte community for your help. Please donate to our organization to help make this project come to life. Your donations will be going towards covering the costs that are for shipping and handling of the bulk order we plan to make for our t-shirts. You can make your donation to our Treasurer, Luisa via her Venmo:&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>RSVP Policy</title><link>https://gwc-uncc.github.io/Girls-Who-Code-at-UNCC/library/rsvp-policy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 22:50:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gwc-uncc.github.io/Girls-Who-Code-at-UNCC/library/rsvp-policy/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="purpose">Purpose&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>The purpose of this policy is to ensure that all of our members abide by their agreement to attend our events that are funded and supply-based. Extensive planning goes into every event(s) we make each school year and we are making this policy mandatory for ALL MEMBERS to follow so that all events that are grant funded or partnered with local/national companies are not wasted. Our e-board strives to provide fun and professional events to everyone so please follow these rules in return. Thank you!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>GWC Merchandise Interest Form</title><link>https://gwc-uncc.github.io/Girls-Who-Code-at-UNCC/library/gwc-merchandise-interest-form/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2022 16:32:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gwc-uncc.github.io/Girls-Who-Code-at-UNCC/library/gwc-merchandise-interest-form/</guid><description>&lt;p>W﻿ant to represent GWC with some cool merch?? We are gathering interests for our first GWC t-shirt through this &lt;a href="https://forms.gle/W1URoNNE5ztSpDmi6">google form&lt;/a>. We hope to start having our GWC t-shirts available in &lt;strong>October&lt;/strong>. More information and details are provided on the form. Feel free to email us at &lt;strong>&lt;a href="mailto:girlswhocodeuncc@gmail.com">girlswhocodeuncc@gmail.com&lt;/a>&lt;/strong> if you have any questions!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Portfolios</title><link>https://gwc-uncc.github.io/Girls-Who-Code-at-UNCC/library/portfolios/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 15:09:31 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://gwc-uncc.github.io/Girls-Who-Code-at-UNCC/library/portfolios/</guid><description>&lt;p>A portfolio is a compilation of things that show your previous work, projects, skills, etc. It helps you go beyond just listing your work history by showing things like specific pieces of work you have created. Nowadays, most portfolios are online websites. But you don&amp;rsquo;t even need to know how to code to build one, as there are many sites that have a drag and drop interface for you to create and host your own website!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Operating Systems</title><link>https://gwc-uncc.github.io/Girls-Who-Code-at-UNCC/library/operating-systems/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 14:32:26 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://gwc-uncc.github.io/Girls-Who-Code-at-UNCC/library/operating-systems/</guid><description>&lt;p>An operating system is the software on your computer that runs all other applications. It allows you to communicate with the computer without having to know how to speak or use the computer&amp;rsquo;s language. &lt;a href="https://edu.gcfglobal.org/en/computerbasics/understanding-operating-systems/1/">Learn More&lt;/a>&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Hackathons</title><link>https://gwc-uncc.github.io/Girls-Who-Code-at-UNCC/library/hackathons/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 14:11:19 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://gwc-uncc.github.io/Girls-Who-Code-at-UNCC/library/hackathons/</guid><description>&lt;p>A hackathon is essentially a short period of time to build a project, typically with a team. These projects, or &amp;lsquo;hacks,&amp;rsquo; are usually created to offer a solution to some type of problem. These &amp;lsquo;problems&amp;rsquo; often times are used as Prize Categories on &lt;a href="https://devpost.com/">Devpost&lt;/a>. You can check out our very first hackathon that GWC and ACMW hosted together &lt;a href="https://bit.ly/axe-hacks">here&lt;/a>!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Command Line Interfaces</title><link>https://gwc-uncc.github.io/Girls-Who-Code-at-UNCC/library/command-line-interface/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 13:45:06 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://gwc-uncc.github.io/Girls-Who-Code-at-UNCC/library/command-line-interface/</guid><description>&lt;p>A Command Line Interface, or CLI, is a &amp;ldquo;text-based user interface (UI) used to run programs, manage computer files and interact with the computer.&amp;rdquo; &lt;a href="https://www.techtarget.com/searchwindowsserver/definition/command-line-interface-CLI">Learn more&lt;/a> about CLIs and check out resources from our &lt;a href="https://docs.google.com/document/d/1fUOufYgRbcGCmlwe0PDt1L7SaFI-rOlK-KjRlsTU5cs/edit?usp=sharing">Command Line Games&lt;/a> event that GWC hosted!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Interviewing &amp; Internships</title><link>https://gwc-uncc.github.io/Girls-Who-Code-at-UNCC/library/interviewing-and-internships/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 13:40:00 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://gwc-uncc.github.io/Girls-Who-Code-at-UNCC/library/interviewing-and-internships/</guid><description>&lt;p>Interviews and internships are an important part of everyone&amp;rsquo;s career journeys. Girls Who Code has had a few events on these topics like how to prepare and panels on other&amp;rsquo;s interviewing or internship experiences. We have also had companies come and speak about their processes and opportunities for college students. You can find some of our recordings and materials &lt;a href="https://docs.google.com/document/d/1fUOufYgRbcGCmlwe0PDt1L7SaFI-rOlK-KjRlsTU5cs/edit?usp=sharing">here&lt;/a>!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Git &amp; GitHub</title><link>https://gwc-uncc.github.io/Girls-Who-Code-at-UNCC/library/git-and-github/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 13:36:06 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://gwc-uncc.github.io/Girls-Who-Code-at-UNCC/library/git-and-github/</guid><description>&lt;p>If you want to develop things, Git is an important software to know and GitHub is a great Git hosting site. Girls Who Code has hosted several workshops involving these two topics, and you can find all materials &lt;a href="https://docs.google.com/document/d/1fUOufYgRbcGCmlwe0PDt1L7SaFI-rOlK-KjRlsTU5cs/edit?usp=sharing">here&lt;/a>.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>UNCC Resources</title><link>https://gwc-uncc.github.io/Girls-Who-Code-at-UNCC/library/uncc-resources/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 13:32:54 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://gwc-uncc.github.io/Girls-Who-Code-at-UNCC/library/uncc-resources/</guid><description>&lt;p>UNC Charlotte has many resources for all sorts of things. It can be hard to realize just how many things are available to you as a student here, especially as a freshman or transfer student. Here we are working on a list of the various resources and opportunities that could be useful to you. Stay tuned!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Web Development</title><link>https://gwc-uncc.github.io/Girls-Who-Code-at-UNCC/library/web-development/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 12:58:17 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://gwc-uncc.github.io/Girls-Who-Code-at-UNCC/library/web-development/</guid><description>&lt;p>Web development is such a great topic to explore nowadays, for everything from building your own portfolio to creating websites or webapps for businesses, clubs, games, etc.! GWC has chosted several workshops involving web development to build online portfolios, and we had our very own Web Team to build this website! You can check out our past event materials &lt;a href="https://docs.google.com/document/d/1fUOufYgRbcGCmlwe0PDt1L7SaFI-rOlK-KjRlsTU5cs/edit?usp=sharing">here&lt;/a>, and you can read more about our Web Team and this website project &lt;a href="../../portfolio/gwc-website-project/">here&lt;/a>.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>